Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Political Science, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1989-079
  - STUDENT FILES
    - Vatcher, William H., Jr., a.b. October 1942 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Wanamaker, A. Temple, a.b. June 1940 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Westcott, William C., a.b. June 1948 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Jr., a.b. June 1933 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Williams, John D., a.b. June 1946 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Wood, James Ralph, a.b. June 1941 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Woodard, Bernice, a.b. June 1932 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Wright, A. Bruce, a.b. June 1932 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Yetter, Corinne C., a.b. June 1944 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence to E. Cottrell (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - STUDENT FILES
    - Bendetson, Karl Robin (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Black, Charles A. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Collett, Merrill J. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Colvin, Howard Milton (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cotter, Cornelius P. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cunningham, J. Lyle (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Fletcher, Charles G. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Fordyce, Jack K. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Foster, Homer (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Gange, John F. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Gill, John Henry (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Gray, Barbara K. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Groff, Katherine (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Gros, Robert R. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Hawkins, Robert Z. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Heard, Townsend (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Holloway, Gilbert (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, John R. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, Martin Lee (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Kennedy, Anthony (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Kilpatrick, Wylie (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Krueger, DeWitt (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Levy, Adoph (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Maghetti, Jack (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Marble, Peter E. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Margulies, Fritz (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - McDowell, Carl E. (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Mellinkoff, Abe I. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Merrill, Dorothea (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Millington, Robert (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Moses, Lincoln E. (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Mueller, Donald (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Muller, Willard (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Munro, William (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Parker, George (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Rich, Robert (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Rowland, Gilford (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Rowland, Mary (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Sawyer, Norman (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Silberman, David B. (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Smith, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Strickler, Dewey (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Sullivan, Lola (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Sussman, Peggy (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Sweet, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Swim, H. Dudley (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Swope, John R. (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Taylor, Marshall K. (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Tenny, Stanley (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Trego, Charlotte (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Tsou, Pang L. (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Ushiro, Arthur K. (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Varanini, Tina (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Vasey, Thomas K. (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Vatcher, William H., Jr. (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Wanamaker, A. Temple (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Westcott, William C. (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Williams, John D. (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Wood, James Ralph (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Woodard, Bernice (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Wright, A.B. (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Yetter, Corinne C. (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1946-54 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1956-57 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1958-59 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1960-61 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1962-63 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1964-66 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1967-68 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Department minutes and memoranda, 1971-73 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Department miscellany (Box 11, Folder 11)